{"items": [{"question": "So thin as to transmit light", "answer": "diaphanous", "options": ["diaphanous", "tyro", "virtuoso", "negligees"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "A loose dressing gown for women", "answer": "negligees", "options": ["negligees", "tyro", "termagant", "virtuoso"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "Someone new to a field or activity", "answer": "tyro", "options": ["virtuoso", "tyro", "termagant", "harridan"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Someone who is dazzlingly skilled in any field", "answer": "virtuoso", "options": ["harridan", "virtuoso", "homonym", "termagant"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "A scolding nagging bad-tempered woman", "answer": "termagant", "options": ["homonym", "homophone", "termagant", "harridan"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "A scolding old woman", "answer": "harridan", "options": ["harridan", "paternal", "homonym", "homophone"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "pronounced or spelled the same way but have different meanings", "answer": "homonym", "options": ["homophone", "maternal", "homonym", "paternal"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "pronounced the same way but differ in meaning", "answer": "homophone", "options": ["homophone", "patrimony", "paternal", "maternal"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "Belonging to one's father", "answer": "paternal", "options": ["paternal", "maternal", "patrimony", "matrimony"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "Belonging to or inherited from one's mother", "answer": "maternal", "options": ["patriarch", "patrimony", "maternal", "matrimony"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "An inheritance coming by right of birth", "answer": "patrimony", "options": ["patrimony", "patriarch", "matriarch", "matrimony"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "spousal relationship", "answer": "matrimony", "options": ["matrimony", "patriarch", "patrician", "matriarch"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "The male head of family or tribe", "answer": "patriarch", "options": ["matriarch", "patrician", "patronize", "patriarch"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "A female head of a family or tribe", "answer": "matriarch", "options": ["patrician", "matriarch", "patronymic", "patronize"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Befitting a person of noble origin", "answer": "patrician", "options": ["patronymic", "patrician", "patronize", "paterfamilias"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "treat like a child", "answer": "patronize", "options": ["patronize", "paterfamilias", "padre", "patronymic"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "derived from a personal or family name", "answer": "patronymic", "options": ["padre", "patronymic", "paterfamilias", "mater"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "The male head of family or tribe", "answer": "paterfamilias", "options": ["padre", "maternity", "mater", "paterfamilias"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "(military) a chaplain in one of the military services", "answer": "padre", "options": ["matron", "padre", "maternity", "mater"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "An informal use of the Latin word for mother", "answer": "mater", "options": ["matron", "mater", "maternity", "alma mater"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "The state of being pregnant", "answer": "maternity", "options": ["patricide", "alma mater", "matron", "maternity"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "A woman in charge of nursing in a medical institution", "answer": "matron", "options": ["matricide", "patricide", "alma mater", "matron"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "school you graduated from", "answer": "alma mater", "options": ["alma mater", "patricide", "suicide", "matricide"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "A person who murders their father", "answer": "patricide", "options": ["matricide", "fratricide", "suicide", "patricide"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "A person who murders their mother", "answer": "matricide", "options": ["infanticide", "fratricide", "matricide", "suicide"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "A person who kills himself intentionally", "answer": "suicide", "options": ["parricide", "fratricide", "suicide", "infanticide"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "A person who murders their brother or sister", "answer": "fratricide", "options": ["sororicide", "parricide", "fratricide", "infanticide"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "A person who murders an infant", "answer": "infanticide", "options": ["parricide", "infanticide", "uxoricide", "sororicide"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "a person who kills his or her parent", "answer": "parricide", "options": ["parricide", "sororicide", "uxoricide", "homicide"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "A person who kills their sister", "answer": "sororicide", "options": ["uxoricide", "sororicide", "manslaughter", "homicide"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "A husband who murders his wife", "answer": "uxoricide", "options": ["uxoricide", "regicide", "manslaughter", "homicide"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "The killing of a human being by another human being", "answer": "homicide", "options": ["genocide", "regicide", "manslaughter", "homicide"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Homicide without malice aforethought", "answer": "manslaughter", "options": ["regicide", "manslaughter", "genocide", "diaphanous"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "The act of killing a king", "answer": "regicide", "options": ["genocide", "diaphanous", "negligees", "regicide"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "The systematic killing of people on the basis of ethnicity, religion, political opinion, social status, etc.", "answer": "genocide", "options": ["diaphanous", "negligees", "tyro", "genocide"], "answer_index": 4}], "title": "Word power Made Easy - Session 29.txt", "total": 35}